Guide to the Intercollegiate Center for Nursing Education Director (Hilda Boerhave Roberts) Papers 1924-2001
Washington State University Libraries Manuscripts, Archives, and Special Collections
- Courses, Series 6
  - Nursing 350: Effects of Environmental Forces - Winter 1973 (Folder 5)
  - Nursing 350: Effects of Environmental Forces - Spring 1974 (Folder 6)
  - Nursing 350: Effects of Environmental Forces - Winter 1974 (Folder 7)
  - Nursing 350: Effects of Environmental Forces - Spring 1975 (Folder 8)
  - Nursing 350: Effects of Environmental Forces - Winter 1975 (Folder 9)
  - Nursing 350: Effects of Environmental Forces - Spring 1976 (Folder 10)
  - Nursing 350: Effects of Environmental Forces - Winter 1977 (Folder 11)
  - Nursing 350: Effects of Environmental Forces - Spring 1977 (Folder 12)
  - Nursing 350: Effects of Environmental Forces - Fall 1977 to Spring 1978 (Folder 13)
  - Nursing 350: Effects of Environmental Forces - Fall 1978 to Spring 1979 (Folder 14)
  - Nursing 350: Effects of Environmental Forces, Archives - 1972 to 1976 (Box 123, Folder 1)
  - Nursing 350: Therapeutic Communication in Nursing - Fall 1987 (Folder 2)
  - Nursing 350: Therapeutic Communication in Nursing - Spring 1989 (Folder 3)
  - Nursing 350: Therapeutic Communication in Nursing - Fall 1989 (Folder 4)
  - Nursing 350: Therapeutic Communication in Nursing - Fall 1990 to Spring 1991 (Folder 5)
  - Nursing 350: Therapeutic Communication in Nursing - Fall 1991 to Spring 1992 (Folder 6)
  - Nursing 350: Therapeutic Communication in Nursing - Fall 1992 to Spring 1993 (Folder 7)
  - Nursing 350: Therapeutic Communication in Nursing - Spring 1994 (Folder 8)
  - Nursing 360: Essentials of Pharmacology - Fall 1976 (Folder 9)
  - Nursing 360: Professional Nursing Concepts and Issues - Spring 1989 (Folder 10)
  - Nursing 360: Professional Nursing Concepts and Issues - Fall 1989 (Folder 11)
  - Nursing 360: Professional Nursing Concepts and Issues - Fall 1990 (Folder 12)
  - Nursing 360: Professional Nursing Concepts and Issues - Fall 1991 (Folder 13)
  - Nursing 360: Professional Nursing Concepts and Issues - Fall 1992 (Folder 14)
  - Nursing 360: Professional Nursing Concepts and Issues - Fall 1993 (Folder 15)
  - Nursing 360: Professional Nursing Concepts and Issues - Fall 1995 (Folder 16)
  - Nursing 364: Nursing Concepts and Practice--Health Assessment for RN Students - Fall 1989 to Spring 1990 (Folder 17)
  - Nursing 364: Nursing Concepts and Practice--Health Assessment for RN Students - Fall 1990 (Folder 18)
  - Nursing 364: Nursing Concepts and Practice--Health Assessment for RN Students - Fall 1991 (Folder 19)
  - Nursing 364: Nursing Concepts and Practice--Health Assessment for RN Students - Fall 1992 (Folder 20)
  - Nursing 364: Nursing Concepts and Practice--Health Assessment for RN Students - Fall 1993 (Folder 21)
  - Nursing 364: Nursing Concepts and Practice--Health Assessment for RN Students - Fall 1994 (Folder 22)
  - Nursing 364: Nursing Concepts and Practice--Health Assessment for RN Students - Fall 1995 (Folder 23)
  - Nursing 364: Nursing Concepts and Practice--Health Assessment for RN Students - Fall 1997 (Folder 24)
  - Nursing 366: Principles of Nursing Medical-Surgical Specialties - Fall 1954 to Spring 1955 (Folder 25)
  - Nursing 366: Principles of Nursing Medical-Surgical Specialties - Fall 1955 to Spring 1956 (Folder 26)
  - Nursing 370: Principles of Nursing Surgical Specialties - Fall 1955 to Spring 1956 (Folder 27)
  - Nursing 370: Nursing Process in Action - Spring 1971 (Folder 28)
  - Nursing 372: Surgical Nursing Specialties Practice - Fall 1955 to Spring 1956 (Folder 29)
  - Nursing 373: Operating Room Practice - Fall 1954 to Spring 1955 (Folder 30)
  - Nursing 380: Principles of Pediatric Nursing - Fall 1954 to Spring 1955 (Folder 31)
  - Nursing 382: Pediatric-Orthopedic Nursing - Fall 1954 to Spring 1955 (Folder 32)
  - Nursing 386: Principles of Obstetrical Nursing - Fall 1954 to Spring 1955 (Folder 33)
  - Nursing 388: Obstetric Nursing Practice - Fall 1954 to Spring 1955 (Folder 34)
  - Nursing 390: Principles of Psychiatric Nursing - Fall 1954 to Spring 1955 (Folder 35)
  - Nursing 391 - Fall 1954 to Spring 1955 (Folder 36)
  - Nursing 395: Advanced Professional Adjustments - Fall 1954 to Spring 1955 (Folder 37)
  - Nursing 396: Introduction to Public Health Nursing - Fall 1954 to Spring 1955 (Folder 38)
  - Nursing 398: Principles of Ward Management and Teaching - 1946 to 1954 (Folder 39)
  - Nursing 398: Nursing Practicum--Advanced Fundamentals - Summer 1993 (Folder 40)
  - Nursing 398: Nursing Practicum--Advanced Fundamentals - Summer 1994 (Folder 41)
  - Nursing 398: Issues in Women's Health--An International Perspective - Fall 1995 (Folder 42)
  - Nursing 398: Special Topics--Concepts of Care - Fall 1997 (Folder 43)
  - Nursing 400: Patient Care Experience - Fall 1957 to Spring 1958 (Folder 44)
  - Nursing 400: Nursing and Aging Population - Fall 1974 (Folder 45)
  - Nursing 401: Nursing Leadership--Research - Spring 1988 (Folder 46)
  - Nursing 401: Nursing Leadership--Research - Fall 1988 to Spring 1989 (Folder 47)
  - Nursing 401: Nursing Leadership--Research - Fall 1989 to Spring 1990 (Folder 48)
  - Nursing 401: Nursing Leadership--Research - Fall 1990 to Spring 1991 (Folder 49)
  - Nursing 401: Nursing Leadership--Research - Fall 1991 to Spring 1992 (Folder 50)
  - Nursing 401: Nursing Leadership--Research - Fall 1992 to Spring 1993 (Folder 51)
  - Nursing 401: Nursing Leadership--Research - Fall 1993 to Spring 1994 (Folder 52)
  - Nursing 401: Nursing Leadership--Research - Fall 1994 to Spring 1995 (Box 124, Folder 1)
  - Nursing 401: Nursing Leadership--Research - Fall 1995 (Folder 2)
  - Nursing 401: Nursing Leadership--Research - Spring 1996 (Folder 3)
  - Nursing 401: Nursing Leadership--Research - Fall 1996 (Folder 4)
  - Nursing 401: Nursing Leadership--Research - Spring 1997 (Folder 5)
  - Nursing 401: Nursing Leadership--Research - Fall 1997 (Folder 6)
  - Nursing 402: Nursing Leadership--Group Therapy and Practice - Spring 1988 (Folder 7)
  - Nursing 402: Nursing Leadership--Group Therapy and Practice - Fall 1988 to Spring 1989 (Folder 8)
  - Nursing 402: Nursing Leadership--Group Therapy and Practice - Fall 1989 to Spring 1990 (Folder 9)
  - Nursing 402: Nursing Leadership--Group Therapy and Practice - Fall 1990 to Spring 1991 (Folder 10)
  - Nursing 402: Nursing Leadership--Group Therapy and Practice - Fall 1991 to Spring 1992 (Folder 11)
  - Nursing 402: Nursing Leadership--Group Therapy and Practice - Fall 1992 to Spring 1993 (Folder 12)
  - Nursing 402: Nursing Leadership--Group Therapy and Practice - Fall 1993 to Spring 1994 (Folder 13)
  - Nursing 402: Nursing Leadership--Group Therapy and Practice - Fall 1994 to Spring 1995 (Folder 14)
  - Nursing 402: Nursing Leadership--Group Therapy and Practice - Fall 1995 (Folder 15)
  - Nursing 402: Nursing Leadership--Group Therapy and Practice - Spring 1996 (Folder 16)
  - Nursing 402: Nursing Leadership--Group Therapy and Practice - Fall 1996 (Folder 17)
  - Nursing 402: Nursing Leadership--Group Therapy and Practice - Spring 1997 (Folder 18)
  - Nursing 402: Nursing Leadership--Group Therapy and Practice - Fall 1997 (Folder 19)
  - Nursing 403: Nursing Leadership--Critical Issues - Spring 1988 (Folder 20)
  - Nursing 403: Nursing Leadership--Critical Issues - Fall 1988 to Spring 1989 (Folder 21)
  - Nursing 403: Nursing Leadership--Critical Issues - Fall 1989 to Spring 1990 (Folder 22)
  - Nursing 403: Nursing Leadership--Critical Issues - Fall 1990 to Spring 1991 (Folder 23)
  - Nursing 403: Nursing Leadership--Critical Issues - Fall 1991 to Spring 1992 (Folder 24)
  - Nursing 403: Nursing Leadership--Critical Issues - Fall 1992 to Spring 1993 (Folder 25)
  - Nursing 403: Nursing Leadership--Critical Issues - Fall 1993 to Spring 1994 (Box 125, Folder 1)
  - Nursing 403: Nursing Leadership--Critical Issues - Fall 1994 to Spring 1995 (Folder 2)
  - Nursing 403: Nursing Leadership--Critical Issues - Fall 1995 (Folder 3)
  - Nursing 403: Nursing Leadership and Management - Spring 1996 (Folder 4)
  - Nursing 403: Nursing Leadership and Management - Fall 1996 (Folder 5)
  - Nursing 403: Nursing Leadership and Management - Spring 1997 (Folder 6)
  - Nursing 403: Nursing Leadership and Management - Fall 1997 (Folder 7)
  - Nursing 405: Introduction to Research - Spring 1980 (Folder 8)
  - Nursing 405: Introduction to Research - Fall 1980 (Folder 9)
  - Nursing 405: Introduction to Research - Spring 1981 (Folder 10)
  - Nursing 405: Introduction to Research - Fall 1981 (Folder 11)
  - Nursing 405: Introduction to Research - Summer 1982 (Folder 12)
  - Nursing 405: Introduction to Research - Fall 1982 (Folder 13)
  - Nursing 406: Clinical Nursing III - Spring 1980 (Box 126, Folder 1)
  - Nursing 406: Clinical Nursing III - Fall 1980 (Folder 2)
  - Nursing 406: Clinical Nursing III - Spring 1981 (Folder 3)
  - Nursing 406: Clinical Nursing III - Fall 1981 (Box 127, Folder 1)
  - Nursing 406: Clinical Nursing III - Spring 1982 (Folder 2)
  - Nursing 406: Clinical Nursing III - Fall 1982 (Box 128, Folder 1)
  - Nursing 416: Clinical Nursing IV - Fall 1980 (Folder 2)
  - Nursing 416: Clinical Nursing IV - Spring 1981 (Folder 3)
  - Nursing 416: Clinical Nursing IV - Fall 1981 (Box 129, Folder 1)
  - Nursing 416: Clinical Nursing IV - Spring 1982 (Folder 2)
  - Nursing 416: Clinical Nursing IV - Fall 1982 (Folder 3)
  - Nursing 420: Nursing Concepts--Adults - Spring 1988 (Folder 4)
  - Nursing 420: Nursing Concepts--Adults - Fall 1988 to Spring 1989 (Folder 5)
  - Nursing 420: Nursing Concepts--Adults - Fall 1989 to Spring 1990 (Folder 6)
  - Nursing 420: Nursing Concepts--Adults - Fall 1990 to Spring 1991 (Folder 7)
  - Nursing 420: Nursing Concepts--Adults - Fall 1991 to Spring 1992 (Folder 8)
  - Nursing 420: Nursing Concepts--Adults - Fall 1992 to Spring 1993 (Folder 9)
  - Nursing 420: Nursing Concepts--Adults - Fall 1993 to Spring 1994 (Folder 10)
  - Nursing 420: Nursing Concepts--Adults - Fall 1994 to Spring 1995 (Folder 11)
  - Nursing 420: Nursing Concepts--Adults - Fall 1995 (Folder 12)
  - Nursing 420: Nursing Concepts--Adults - Spring 1996 (Folder 13)
  - Nursing 420: Nursing Concepts--Adults - Fall 1996 (Folder 14)
  - Nursing 420: Nursing Concepts--Adults - Spring 1997 (Folder 15)
  - Nursing 420: Nursing Concepts--Adults - Fall 1997 (Folder 16)
  - Nursing 421: Nursing Practice--Adults - Spring 1988 (Folder 17)
  - Nursing 421: Nursing Practice--Adults - Fall 1988 to Spring 1989 (Folder 18)
  - Nursing 421: Nursing Practice--Adults - Fall 1989 to Spring 1990 (Folder 19)
  - Nursing 421: Nursing Practice--Adults - Fall 1990 to Spring 1991 (Folder 20)
  - Nursing 421: Nursing Practice--Adults - Fall 1991 to Spring 1992 (Box 130, Folder 1)
  - Nursing 421: Nursing Practice--Adults - Fall 1992 (Folder 2)
  - Nursing 421: Nursing Practice--Adults - Spring 1993 (Folder 3)
  - Nursing 421: Nursing Practice--Adults - Fall 1993 (Folder 4)
  - Nursing 421: Nursing Practice--Adults - Spring 1994 (Folder 5)
  - Nursing 421: Nursing Practice--Adults - Fall 1994 (Folder 6)
  - Nursing 421: Nursing Practice--Adults- Spring 1995 (Box 131, Folder 1)
  - Nursing 421: Nursing Practice--Adults - Fall 1995 (Folder 2)
  - Nursing 421: Nursing Practice--Adults - Spring 1996 (Folder 3)
  - Nursing 421: Nursing Practice--Adults - Fall 1996 (Folder 4)
  - Nursing 421: Nursing Practice--Adults - Spring 1997 (Folder 5)
  - Nursing 421: Nursing Practice--Adults - Fall 1997 (Box 132, Folder 1)
  - Nursing 440: Community Health Nursing - Fall 1968 to Spring 1969 (Folder 2)
  - Nursing 440: Community Health Nursing - Fall 1970 to Spring 1971 (Folder 3)
  - Nursing 440: Community Health Nursing - Fall 1971 to Spring 1972 (Folder 4)
  - Nursing 440: Community Health Nursing - Fall 1972 to Spring 1973 (Folder 5)
  - Nursing 440: Community Health Nursing - Fall 1973 (Folder 6)
  - Nursing 440: Community Health Nursing - Winter 1973-1974 (Folder 7)
  - Nursing 440: Community Health Nursing - Spring 1974 (Folder 8)
  - Nursing 440: Community Health Nursing - Fall 1974 (Folder 9)
  - Nursing 440: Community Health Nursing - Winter 1974-1975 (Folder 10)
  - Nursing 440: Community Health Nursing - Spring 1975 (Box 133, Folder 1)
  - Nursing 440: Community Health Nursing - Fall 1975 (1 of 2) (Folder 2)
  - Nursing 440: Community Health Nursing - Fall 1975 (2 of 2) (Folder 3)
  - Nursing 440: Community Health Nursing - Winter 1975-1976 (Folder 4)
  - Nursing 440: Community Health Nursing - Spring 1976 (1 of 2) (Folder 5)
  - Nursing 440: Community Health Nursing - Spring 1976 (2 of 2) (Folder 6)
  - Nursing 440: Community Health Nursing - Winter 1976 (Folder 7)
  - Nursing 440: Community Health Nursing - Fall 1976 to Spring 1977 (1 of 2) (Folder 8)
  - Nursing 440: Community Health Nursing - Fall 1976 to Spring 1977 (2 of 2) (Box 134, Folder 1)
  - Nursing 440: Community Health Nursing - 1974 to 1978 (Folder 2)
  - Nursing 440: Community Health Nursing - Fall 1977 to spring 1978 (Folder 3)
  - Nursing 440: Community Health Nursing - Fall 1978 (Folder 4)
  - Nursing 440: Community Health Nursing - Winter 1978 to Spring 1979 (Box 135, Folder 1)
  - Nursing 440: Community Health Nursing - Fall 1979 (Folder 2)
  - Nursing 440: Community Health Nursing - Spring 1980 (Folder 3)
  - Nursing 440: Community Health Nursing - Fall 1980 (Folder 4)
  - Nursing 440: Community Health Nursing- Fall 1980 Outreach (Box 136, Folder 1)
  - Nursing 440: Community Health Nursing - Winter 1980 (Folder 2)
  - Nursing 440: Nursing Concepts--Community Health - Spring 1988 (Folder 3)
  - Nursing 440: Nursing Concepts--Community Health - Fall 1988 to Spring 1989 (Folder 4)
  - Nursing 440: Nursing Concepts--Community Health - Fall 1989 to Spring 1990 (Folder 5)
  - Nursing 440: Nursing Concepts--Community Health - Fall 1990 to Spring 1991 (Folder 6)
  - Nursing 440: Nursing Concepts--Community Health - Fall 1991 to Spring 1992 (Folder 7)
  - Nursing 440: Nursing Concepts--Community Health - Fall 1992 to Spring 1993 (Folder 8)
  - Nursing 440: Nursing Concepts--Community Health - Fall 1993 to Spring 1994 (Box 137, Folder 1)
  - Nursing 440: Nursing Concepts--Community Health - Fall 1994 to Spring 1995 (Folder 2)
  - Nursing 440: Nursing Concepts--Community Health - Fall 1995 (Folder 3)
  - Nursing 440: Nursing Concepts--Community Health - Spring 1996 (Folder 4)
  - Nursing 440: Nursing Concepts--Community Health - Fall 1996 (Folder 5)
  - Nursing 440: Nursing Concepts--Community Health - Spring 1997 (Folder 6)
  - Nursing 440: Nursing Concepts--Community Health - Fall 1997 (Folder 7)
  - Nursing 440: Nursing Concepts--Community Health, Archives - 1972 to 1979 (Folder 8)
  - Nursing 440: Nursing Concepts--Community Health, Archives - 1976 to 1980 (Folder 9)
  - Nursing 441: Community Health Nursing Practicum - Fall 1970 to Spring 1971 (Folder 10)
  - Nursing 441: Community Health Nursing Practicum - Fall 1971 to Spring 1972 (Box 138, Folder 1)
  - Nursing 441: Nursing Practice--Community Health - Spring 1988 (Folder 2)
  - Nursing 441: Nursing Practice--Community Health - Fall 1988 to Spring 1989 (Folder 3)
  - Nursing 441: Nursing Practice--Community Health - Fall 1989 to Spring 1990 (Folder 4)
  - Nursing 441: Nursing Practice--Community Health - Fall 1990 to Spring 1991 (Folder 5)
  - Nursing 441: Nursing Practice--Community Health - Fall 1991 to Spring 1992 (Folder 6)
  - Nursing 441: Nursing Practice--Community Health - Fall 1992 (Folder 7)
  - Nursing 441: Nursing Practice--Community Health - Spring 1993 (Folder 8)
  - Nursing 441: Nursing Practice--Community Health - Fall 1993 (Folder 9)
  - Nursing 441: Nursing Practice--Community Health - Spring 1994 (Folder 10)
  - Nursing 441: Nursing Practice--Community Health - Fall 1994 (Box 139, Folder 1)
  - Nursing 441: Nursing Practice--Community Health - Spring 1995 (Folder 2)
  - Nursing 441: Nursing Practice--Community Health - Fall 1995 (Folder 3)
  - Nursing 441: Nursing Practice--Community Health - Spring 1996 (Folder 4)
  - Nursing 441: Nursing Practice--Community Health - Fall 1996 (Folder 5)
  - Nursing 441: Nursing Practice--Community Health - Spring 1997 (1 of 2) (Folder 6)
  - Nursing 441: Nursing Practice--Community Health - Spring 1997 (2 of 2) (Folder 7)
  - Nursing 441: Nursing Practice--Community Health - Fall 1997 (Box 140, Folder 1)
  - Nursing 450: Survey of Nursing II - Fall 1970 to Spring 1971 (Folder 2)
  - Nursing 450: Survey of Nursing II - Fall 1971 to Spring 1972 (Folder 3)
  - Nursing 450: Survey of Nursing II - Fall 1972 to Spring 1973 (Folder 4)
  - Nursing 450: Survey of Nursing II - Fall 1973 (Folder 5)
  - Nursing 450: Survey of Nursing II - Winter 1973 (Folder 6)
  - Nursing 450: Survey of Nursing II - Spring 1974 (Folder 7)
  - Nursing 450: Trends and Issues in Nursing - Fall 1975 (Folder 8)
  - Nursing 450: Trends and Issues in Nursing - Winter 1975 (Folder 9)
  - Nursing 450: Trends and Issues in Nursing - Spring 1976 (Folder 10)
  - Nursing 450: Trends and Issues in Nursing - Fall 1976 (Folder 11)
  - Nursing 450: Trends and Issues in Nursing - Winter 1977 (Folder 12)
  - Nursing 450: Trends and Issues in Nursing - Spring 1977 (Folder 13)
  - Nursing 450: Trends and Issues in Nursing - Fall 1977 to Spring 1978 (Folder 14)
  - Nursing 450: Trends and Issues in Nursing - Fall 1978 to Spring 1979 (Folder 15)
  - Nursing 450: Trends and Issues in Nursing - Fall 1979 (Folder 16)
  - Nursing 450: Nursing Concepts - Spring 1988 (Box 141, Folder 1)
  - Nursing 450: Nursing Concepts - Fall 1988 to Spring 1989 (Folder 2)
  - Nursing 450: Nursing Concepts - Fall 1989 to Spring 1990 (Folder 3)
  - Nursing 450: Nursing Concepts - Fall 1990 to Spring 1991 (Folder 4)
  - Nursing 450: Nursing Concepts - Fall 1991 to Spring 1992 (Folder 5)
  - Nursing 450: Nursing Concepts - Fall 1992 to Spring 1993 (Folder 6)
  - Nursing 450: Nursing Concepts - Fall 1993 to Spring 1994 (Folder 7)
  - Nursing 450: Nursing Concepts - Fall 1994 to Spring 1995 (Folder 8)
  - Nursing 450: Nursing Concepts - Fall 1995 (Folder 9)
  - Nursing 450: Nursing Concepts - Spring 1996 (Folder 10)
  - Nursing 450: Nursing Concepts - Fall 1996 (Folder 11)
  - Nursing 450: Nursing Concepts - Spring 1997 (Folder 12)
  - Nursing 450: Nursing Concepts - Fall 1997 (Folder 13)
  - Nursing 450: Nursing Concepts, Archives - 1974 to 1976 (Folder 14)
  - Nursing 450: Nursing Concepts, Supplemental Materials - 1973 to 1974 (Folder 15)
  - Nursing 450: Nursing Concepts, UNIPAC - 1973 to 1975 (Folder 16)
  - Nursing 451: Nursing Practice--Psychiatric/Mental Health - Spring 1988 (Folder 17)
  - Nursing 451: Nursing Practice--Psychiatric/Mental Health - Fall 1988 to Spring 1989 (Folder 18)
  - Nursing 451: Nursing Practice--Psychiatric/Mental Health - Fall 1989 to Spring 1990 (Folder 19)
  - Nursing 451: Nursing Practice--Psychiatric/Mental Health - Fall 1990 to Spring 1991 (Folder 20)
  - Nursing 451: Nursing Practice--Psychiatric/Mental Health - Fall 1991 to Spring 1992 (Box 142, Folder 1)
  - Nursing 451: Nursing Practice--Psychiatric/Mental Health - Fall 1992 to Spring 1993 (Folder 2)
  - Nursing 451: Nursing Practice--Psychiatric/Mental Health - Fall 1993 to Spring 1994 (Folder 3)
  - Nursing 451: Nursing Practice--Psychiatric/Mental Health - Fall 1994 to Spring 1995 (Folder 4)
  - Nursing 451: Nursing Practice--Psychiatric/Mental Health - Fall 1995 (Folder 5)
  - Nursing 451: Nursing Practice--Psychiatric/Mental Health - Spring 1996 (Folder 6)
  - Nursing 451: Nursing Practice--Psychiatric/Mental Health - Fall 1996 (Folder 7)
  - Nursing 451: Nursing Practice--Psychiatric/Mental Health - Spring 1997 (Folder 8)
  - Nursing 451: Nursing Practice--Psychiatric/Mental Health - Fall 1997 (Box 143, Folder 1)
  - Nursing 460: Psychiatric Nursing - Fall 1968 to Spring 1969 (Folder 2)
  - Nursing 460: Psychiatric Nursing - Fall 1970 to Spring 1971 (Folder 3)
  - Nursing 460: Psychiatric Nursing - Spring 1971 (Folder 4)
  - Nursing 460: Psychiatric Nursing - Fall 1971 to Spring 1972 (Folder 5)
  - Nursing 460: Psychiatric Nursing - Fall 1972 to Spring 1973 (Folder 6)
  - Nursing 460: Psychiatric Nursing - Fall 1973 (Folder 7)
  - Nursing 460: Psychiatric Nursing - Winter 1973-1974 (Folder 8)
  - Nursing 460: Psychiatric Nursing - Fall 1974 (Folder 9)
  - Nursing 460: Psychiatric Nursing - Winter 1974-1975 (Box 144, Folder 1)
  - Nursing 460: Psychiatric Nursing - Spring 1975 (Folder 2)
  - Nursing 460: Psychiatric Nursing - Fall 1975 to Spring 1976 (Folder 3)
  - Nursing 460: Psychiatric Nursing - Fall 1976 to Spring 1977 (Folder 4)
  - Nursing 460: Psychiatric Nursing - Fall 1977 to Spring 1978 (Folder 5)
  - Nursing 460: Psychiatric Nursing - Fall 1978 to Spring 1979 (Folder 6)
  - Nursing 460: Psychiatric Nursing - Fall 1979 to Spring 1980 (1 of 2) (Box 145, Folder 1)
  - Nursing 460: Psychiatric Nursing - Fall 1979 to Spring 1980 (2 of 2) (Folder 2)
  - Nursing 460: Psychiatric Nursing (Outreach) - Fall 1979 to Spring 1980 (Folder 3)
  - Nursing 460: Psychiatric Nursing - Summer 1980 (Folder 4)
  - Nursing 460: Psychiatric Nursing - Spring 1981 (Box 146, Folder 1)
  - Nursing 460: Nursing Concepts--Clinical Decision-Making - Fall 1989 (Folder 2)
  - Nursing 460: Nursing Concepts--Clinical Decision-Making - Spring 1991 (Folder 3)
  - Nursing 460: Nursing Concepts--Clinical Decision-Making - Spring 1992 (Folder 4)
  - Nursing 460: Nursing Concepts--Clinical Decision-Making - Spring 1993 (Folder 5)
  - Nursing 460: Nursing Concepts--Clinical Decision-Making - Spring 1996 (Folder 6)
  - Nursing 460: Nursing Concepts--Clinical Decision-Making - Spring 1997 (Folder 7)
  - Nursing 460: Nursing Concepts--Clinical Decision-Making, Archives - 1973 to 1979 (Folder 8)
  - Nursing 460: Nursing Concepts--Clinical Decision-Making, Archives - 1976 to 1980 (Folder 9)
  - Nursing 461: Psychiatric Nursing Practicum - Fall 1970 to Spring 1971 (Folder 10)
  - Nursing 461: Psychiatric Nursing Practicum - Fall 1971 to Spring 1972 (Folder 11)
  - Nursing 461: Nursing Practice Clinical Decision-Making - Fall 1989 (Folder 12)
  - Nursing 461: Nursing Practice Clinical Decision-Making - Spring 1991 (Folder 13)
  - Nursing 461: Nursing Practice Clinical Decision-Making - Spring 1992 (Folder 14)
  - Nursing 461: Nursing Practice Clinical Decision-Making - Spring 1993 (Folder 15)
  - Nursing 461: Nursing Practice Clinical Decision-Making - Spring 1995 (Folder 16)
  - Nursing 462: Selected Nursing Concepts--Psychiatric/Mental Health - Spring 1990 (Folder 17)
  - Nursing 462: Selected Nursing Concepts--Psychiatric/Mental Health - Spring 1991 (Folder 18)
  - Nursing 462: Selected Nursing Concepts--Psychiatric/Mental Health - Fall 1991 (Folder 19)
  - Nursing 462: Selected Nursing Concepts--Psychiatric/Mental Health - Fall 1992 (Folder 20)
  - Nursing 462: Selected Nursing Concepts--Psychiatric/Mental Health - Fall 1993 (Folder 21)
  - Nursing 462: Selected Nursing Concepts--Psychiatric/Mental Health - Fall 1995 (Folder 22)
  - Nursing 463: Psychiatric-Mental Health Nursing Practice--Individuals, Families, Groups (Folder 23)
  - Nursing 463: Psychiatric-Mental Health Nursing Practice--Individuals, Families, Groups - Spring 1990 (Folder 24)
  - Nursing 463: Psychiatric-Mental Health Nursing Practice--Individuals, Families, Groups - Spring 1991 (Folder 25)
  - Nursing 463: Psychiatric-Mental Health Nursing Practice--Individuals, Families, Groups - Fall 1991 (Folder 26)
  - Nursing 463: Psychiatric-Mental Health Nursing Practice--Individuals, Families, Groups - Fall 1992 (Folder 27)
  - Nursing 463: Psychiatric-Mental Health Nursing Practice--Individuals, Families, Groups - Fall 1993 (Folder 28)
  - Nursing 466: Nursing Leadership/Management--Concepts and Principles - Spring 1990 (Folder 29)
  - Nursing 466: Nursing Leadership/Management--Concepts and Principles - Spring 1991 (Folder 30)